<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://baalkikhaal.github.io/rss-feed-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-23T00:54:23.191Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://baalkikhaal.github.io/rss-feed-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://baalkikhaal.github.io/rss-feed-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript - A Free 7-hour Interactive Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60a36742906c5207e3a7da6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-interactive-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last four months, I have recorded what is probably the most interactive JavaScript course that has ever been created. The reason I have done this is because I often see new coders fall into the same pitfalls again and again when trying to learn JavaScript, with the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors to Style Your Web Page]]></title>
        <id>60a341f5906c5207e3a7da61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-css-selectors-to-style-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors are one of the most important parts of CSS. They give you the ability to target HTML elements on your web page that you want to style. Without CSS selectors, you wouldn't be able to style your page to look how you want. Thankfully CSS selectors have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web3? The Decentralized Internet of the Future Explained]]></title>
        <id>60a42386906c5207e3a7dfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is going through a paradigm shift. Learn the differences between Web2 and Web3, and why many developers and companies are shifting their approach in building apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize for Change in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>60a469ec906c5207e3a7e1b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-for-change-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you work at Magic Money Corp, which runs on just three lines of JavaScript: let input = { step1: 'collect underpants' } doStuff(input)  profit(input) // $$$!!! Now imagine that something's wrong with doStuff and you need to take it down for maintenance. What happens if you temporarily comment out the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break into Ethereum, Crypto, and Web3 as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60a53182906c5207e3a7e588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breaking-into-ethereum-crypto-web3-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I've been talking about my move into the Web3, Ethereum, and crypto space since making the switch from a traditional web, mobile, and cloud background. Since making that move, a shocking number of people have reached out to me who are also thinking about doing the same.  It's really]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Development Pricing Guide – Should Freelancers Bill by the Hour?]]></title>
        <id>60a3780f906c5207e3a7db5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you offer your services as a freelance developer, you have a major say in how you price your project.  But how do you go about charging for a website project? "Well, I just bill by the hour and send an invoice every week or month." ...I hear you say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Programs – 101 Ways to Learn to Code for Free]]></title>
        <id>6068f146d5756f080ba9402d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-programs-101-ways-to-learn-to-code-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, you can learn to code for free, from the convenience of your own home, and at your own pace. I'm going to show you 101 courses where you can learn computer science and programming for free.  The freeCodeCamp courses are completely free and some of them include a free]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a Keras SavedModel into a Browser-based Web App]]></title>
        <id>609bea6b62ab9107fe5a9f89</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/convert-keras-savedmodel-into-browser-based-webapp/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a Python developer who works with Keras SavedModels, this article is for you.  Perhaps you're not sure how to use SavedModels to leverage the power of machine learning in browser-based web apps. But don't worry – we'll cover all the basic steps you need to get started.  Along with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redux for Beginners – Learn Redux Basics with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>609fc4cc62ab9107fe5aac91</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/redux-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux can be confusing for beginner React developers to understand. There are a lot of concepts you need to know to use it properly, like reducers, actions, store, pure functions, immutability, and much more. But every React developer should know the basics of how to work with Redux, since industry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Be a Successful Entrepreneur – A Developer&#x27;s Guide to Startup Strategy and Design]]></title>
        <id>60685767d5756f080ba93df4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/be-a-successful-entrepreneur-developers-guide-to-startup-strategy-and-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to freeCodeCamp’s 2018 New Coder Survey, 40.3% of participants want to build a business of their own, either as a freelancer or as an entrepreneur.  If you are in that 40.3%, then this article is for you. If you are in the remaining 59.7%, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML vs JSX – What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60a2771762ab9107fe5ab383</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-vs-jsx-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T21:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML vs JSX Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) is the standard language for documents that determine the structure of a web page.  HTML is a very important language in web development. Your code is either in HTML originally or compiles to it so browsers can read it.  JSX, on the other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete Guide to Full Stack Ethereum Development]]></title>
        <id>60a536e1906c5207e3a7e6b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/full-stack-ethereum-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to build full stack dApps with React, Ethers.js, Solidity, and Hardhat. You can find the code for this project here. The video course for this tutorial is here. I recently joined Edge & Node as a Developer Relations Engineer and have been diving]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DOM Explained for Beginners – How the Document Object Model Works]]></title>
        <id>60a16df162ab9107fe5ab01b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-explained-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-document-object-model/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I started out as a web developer, people often threw around the term "DOM" in the industry. Every JavaScript tutorial mentioned it, but I didn't know what it meant. Fast forward two years, and now that I know what it's all about, I am going to explain what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Lottie Library like a Pro – Lottie Resources for Designers and Developers]]></title>
        <id>609f552e62ab9107fe5aaba0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lottie-like-a-pro-resources-for-designers-and-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lottie is a library that helps render Adobe After Effects animations natively on mobile and the web. I like using Lottie for animations in my projects because: Creating an animation from scratch can be time-consuming, andGIF files can be double the size of Lottie JSON files (the files containing the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solidity Tutorial – How to Create NFTs with Hardhat]]></title>
        <id>609cb90262ab9107fe5aa026</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solidity-tutorial-hardhat-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a developer who's mostly been writing JavaScript, so the Solidity development environment was a bit hard to learn.  About four months ago, I switched to Hardhat from Truffle. This cool new kid on the block drastically improved my coding experience. So today I want to share it with my]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T09:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SendGrid? SMTP Email Newsletter Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>609d63e962ab9107fe5aa2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sendgrid-smpt-email-newsletter-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of the term SMTP before, and wondered what it is. SMTP is a common method for handling email messages. Today I am going to explain what SMTP is, and how to use an SMTP provider such as SendGrid to send emails from your address. What Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React for Beginners: Complete React Cheatsheet for 2021]]></title>
        <id>609ea83362ab9107fe5aa920</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the React for Beginners guide. It's designed to teach you all the core React concepts that you need to know to start building React applications in 2021. I created this resource to give you the most complete and beginner-friendly path to learn React from the ground up. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development for Beginners – Learn Basic HTML and CSS to Build Your First Web Page]]></title>
        <id>609e8c2162ab9107fe5aa77d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-development-for-beginners-basic-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites are built and designed? Do you want to learn the art of web development but you're not that tech savvy – yet? Well, then this tutorial is for you. It's an introduction to Web Development for beginners so you can learn the basics even if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Email Newsletter [2021 Tutorial] – Design, Layout, Send]]></title>
        <id>609414f32cd0545b5e943526</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-email-newsletter-design-layout-send/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T21:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a large community, chances are you need a way to communicate updates to your members quickly and efficiently. An email newsletter can be a very effective way to do so. In this article, I am going to provide some tips and suggestions for maximizing the impact and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? The 10 Most Common Types of Tests Developers Use in Projects]]></title>
        <id>609952396008950828b3ea8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and testing go hand in hand. And in the era of agile software development, with quick releases of small iterations, you should do testing more and more frequently.  In order to perform effective testing, you need to know about the different types of testing and when you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Tutorial – How to Work with Multiple Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>609bcc6a62ab9107fe5a9f08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-multiple-checkboxes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling multiple checkboxes in React is completely different from how you use regular HTML checkboxes. So in this article, we'll see how to work with multiple checkboxes in React. You will learn: How to use a checkbox as a Controlled Input in ReactHow to use the array map and reduce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Lawyer to Engineer at Google – How to Switch Careers and Learn New Skills]]></title>
        <id>609ccb0d62ab9107fe5aa0ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-lawyer-to-google-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a corporate lawyer for 12 years. I never thought I'd be working at Google as a software engineer, but now I am. And I'm going to share with you ten important lessons I learned during this career transition. I finished law school in Bangalore, India, a year before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing TypeScript 4.3 RC]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/?p=2970</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-3-rc/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T22:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we&#8217;re excited to announce our Release Candidate (RC) of TypeScript 4.3! Between now and the stable release of TypeScript 4.2, we expect no further changes apart from critical bug fixes.
The post Announcing TypeScript 4.3 RC appeared first on TypeScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Rosenwasser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Portfolio with Vue.JS, Axios, the GitHub REST API, and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>5fde208ae6787e09839407c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-portfolio-with-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we will build two simple projects and deploy them on Netlify. We will use Vue.js as our front-end framework, and use different technologies to build our projects.  If you follow this tutorial to the end, you will build a simplified version of Twitter and a single]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the Kivy Python Library to Create Games and Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>609c215862ab9107fe5a9fa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-the-kivy-python-library-to-create-games-and-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kivy is a free and open source Python framework for developing mobile apps and games with a natural user interface. We just released a 5-hour Kivy course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this Kivy course, you will learn to create games and applications with Python for every platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Selenium and Python to Scrape Websites More Effectively]]></title>
        <id>6096aafe2cd0545b5e944430</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-web-scraping-with-selenium/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're scraping data from the web with Python, Selenium will often come up as an helpful tool to use. It was originally designed for automated testing, but its scraping capabilities are impressive, too. This is because Selenium can do things that other libraries or frameworks often can't when collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Résumé – Practical Guide with Example Résumé]]></title>
        <id>6093929601fc34080ef81a0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-resume-with-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a résumé can be a little intimidating. And the pressure to make it really good and fill in each detail can be tiresome and scary. This is especially true if you're doing it for the first time, because you might not know what to add in or what to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Beautiful Page Transitions in Angular]]></title>
        <id>609a73156008950828b3f2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beautiful-page-transitions-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world, just having a website is not enough. The website needs to have a clean UI and it needs to be intuitive. And most importantly, it needs to have some sort of interactive element. Interactivity keeps users glued to your site for longer periods of time. As]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Job by Building Relationships – Advice from a Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>609552842cd0545b5e943bcd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-job-by-building-relationships/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The job search is exhausting. You apply to countless jobs through LinkedIn and company websites. Apply, apply, apply. Submit, submit, submit. You're tired.  But you know that's not even the worst part. The worst part is the black hole your applications seem to fall into 95% of the time. Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Hash Table – Associative Array Hashing in JS]]></title>
        <id>60856789dd38b9088c2bf4ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-hash-table-associative-array-hashing-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hash Tables are a data structure that allow you to create a list of paired values. You can then retrieve a certain value by using the key for that value, which you put into the table beforehand. A Hash Table transforms a key into an integer index using a hash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Start Using Chakra UI]]></title>
        <id>60977de12cd0545b5e944661</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-should-you-start-using-chakraui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll talk about what ChakraUI is and why you should use it.  Chakra UI is a component-based library. It's made up of basic building blocks that can help you build the front-end of your web application.  It is customizable and reusable, and most importantly it supports ReactJs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Good Typography - Free Treehouse Course]]></title>
        <id>60998ee76008950828b3ed10</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-design-good-typography/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typography is one of the most important aspects of good design. It is especially important for web designers. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all you need to know about creating good typography as a UX Designer. Hope Armstrong developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First Developer Job through Intelligent, Genuine Networking]]></title>
        <id>605cf4879618b008528a77e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/networking-for-aspiring-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T01:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's not about what you know, it's about whom you know." "70-80% of jobs are found via someone's network." Most of us have heard cliches and stats like the above. And I think most of us intuitively know that having a network of people that can help us find opportunities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ace Your Coding Interview – Advice from a Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>60953e202cd0545b5e943a8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-acing-your-coding-interview-advice-from-senior-software-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical interviews are one of the most stressful parts of landing a job in tech.  You don't know what questions the interviewer is going to ask. What if you have no idea how to solve the problem in front of you? What if you freeze up and look like you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (&lt;time&gt;) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Systems Book Recommendations – Learn How to Build and Understand ML Systems]]></title>
        <id>609558382cd0545b5e943c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-systems-book-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life.” ― Mark TwainI hope you’re reading this blog in your pjs looking forward to a rejuvenating and healthy weekend.  I have been working on multiple projects lately, from creating Machine Learing Engineering and Machine Learning Operations courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion Might Seem Scary – But it Doesn&#x27;t Have to Be]]></title>
        <id>609551f02cd0545b5e943bc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-doesnt-have-to-be-scary/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any concept that we don't fully understand can be scary at first. Recursion is a topic that programming students don't learn right away. But that doesn't mean it needs to be scary or cause anxiety. In fact, recursion is a concept that we can define rather simply. According to Wikipedia:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is &quot;Lifting State Up&quot; in React?]]></title>
        <id>609409c201fc34080ef81f97</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-lifting-state-up-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a simple and practical example what it means to "lift state up" in React, and how it can help you build your applications. Lifting state up is a common pattern that is essential for React developers to know. It helps you avoid more complex (and often unnecessary) patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use the Chrome DevTools to Troubleshoot Websites]]></title>
        <id>609415eb2cd0545b5e943534</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-use-the-chrome-devtools-to-troubleshoot-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome DevTools is a set of web developer tools built directly into the Google Chrome browser. They can be super helpful for web developers. We just published a crash course that will teach you how to use Chrome DevTools to improve your productivity as a web developer. You will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional Types in Swift – How to Use and Unwrap Optionals]]></title>
        <id>60939bde01fc34080ef81a19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-types-in-swift/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coming from Java, C++, or other object-oriented languages, chances are that you've never come across optional types or "optionals". And you might be quite surprised to know that such a concept exists in Swift. Optionals are a fundamental topic that you need to thoroughly understand to code in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python and OpenCV Course –Create Computer Vision Apps in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>609307e801fc34080ef8191e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-computer-vision-apps-in-the-cloud-with-opencv-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCV is a library of programming functions mainly aimed at real-time computer vision.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use OpenCV in the cloud with Python. Misbah Mohammed created this course. He has a lot of experience with machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.6]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: The output website didn't have favicon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Item description didn't use the description property from feed item.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: MIT license
Added: cache.json is stamped with the version of the builder. This allows future builder with breaking change to ignore incompatible cache.
Added: Feed source retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Item enrichment retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Console log for cache restore and update behavior.
Added: npx command: npx osmosfeed
Changed: Improved console log that breaks down rendered item count into "new" and "cached".
Fixed: Item…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Async Await Tutorial – With Asynchronous JavaScript Examples]]></title>
        <id>609011fd8eb3fb07cf09a034</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-async-await-tutorial-with-asynchronous-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete guide to Node.js async await]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy a Directory in Linux – How to cp a Folder in the Command Line in Linux and Unix (MacOS)]]></title>
        <id>608f5ad48eb3fb07cf099ddb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-a-directory-in-linux-how-to-cp-a-folder-in-the-command-line-in-linux-and-unix-macos/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T15:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To copy files or directories in Unix-based operating systems (Linux and MacOS), you use the cp command. The cp command is a relatively simple command, but its behavior changes slightly depending on the inputs (files vs directories) and the options you pass to it. To view the documentation or manual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fetch Data in React from a GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>6090187c8eb3fb07cf09a060</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-ways-to-fetch-data-react-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T17:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go through the five best ways that you can fetch data with React from a GraphQL API. While there are a couple of popular libraries which are made to interact with GraphQL APIs from a React application, there are many different ways to fetch data with GraphQL. I've included]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internal Combustion Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://ciechanow.ski/internal-combustion-engine/</id>
        <link href="https://ciechanow.ski/internal-combustion-engine/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The invention of the internal combustion engine in the 19th century has revolutionized transportation over land, water, and air. Despite their omnipresence in modern day, the operation of an engine may be cryptic. Over the course of this article I&rsquo;d like to explain the functionality of all the basic engine parts shown in the demonstration below. You can drag it around to see it from other angles:

This article has many interactive demonstrations which are best seen .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bartosz Ciechanowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing GR with Shadows and Quasinormal Modes]]></title>
        <id>http://physicsforme.com/?p=11125</id>
        <link href="https://physicsforme.com/2021/04/28/testing-gr-with-shadows-and-quasinormal-modes/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>physicsgg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID vaccines and blood clots: five key questions]]></title>
        <id>http://physicsforme.com/?p=11121</id>
        <link href="https://physicsforme.com/2021/04/24/covid-vaccines-and-blood-clots-five-key-questions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-24T10:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a difficult week for two COVID-19 vaccines. On 13 April, US regulators urged health-care providers to temporarily stop using a vaccine made by Johnson &#38; Johnson (J&#38;J) of New Brunswick, New Jersey, because of six suspected cases of unusual blood clotting among nearly seven million vaccine recipients. The move came after European [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>physicsgg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Maldacena: Black Holes, Hawking Radiation and the Nature of Spacetime]]></title>
        <id>http://physicsforme.com/?p=11118</id>
        <link href="https://physicsforme.com/2021/04/23/juan-maldacena-black-holes-hawking-radiation-and-the-nature-of-spacetime/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T14:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>physicsgg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>